<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MotionLayout</string>
    <string name="animation1">Animation1</string>
    <string name="Animation1">animation1</string>
    <string name="Animation2">animation2</string>
    <string name="Animation3">animation3</string>
    <string name="Animation4">animation4</string>
    <string name="Animation5">animation5</string>
    <string name="Animation6">animation6</string>
    <string name="the_labrador_retriever_was_bred_to_be_both_a_friendly_companion_and_a_useful_working_dog_breed_historically_they_earned_their_keep_as_fishermen_s_helpers_hauling_nets_fetching_ropes_and_retrieving_fish_from_the_chilly_north_atlantic">The Labrador Retriever was bred to be both a friendly companion and a useful working dog breed. Historically, they earned their keep as fishermen’s helpers: hauling nets, fetching ropes, and retrieving fish from the chilly North Atlantic.</string>
    <string name="explore_the_labrador">Explore the Labrador</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="one">one</string>
    <string name="two">two</string>
    <string name="three">three</string>
    <string name="four">four</string>
    <string name="five">five</string>
    <string name="six">six</string>
    <string name="seven">seven</string>
    <string name="eight">eight</string>
    <string name="nine">nine</string>
    <string name="asterisk">asterisk</string>
    <string name="zero">zero</string>
    <string name="sharp">sharp</string>
    <string name="fourth">fourth</string>
    <string name="third">third</string>
    <string name="second">second</string>
    <string name="first">first</string>
    <string name="swipe">swipe</string>
    <string name="california">california</string>
    <string name="sight_seeing">sight_seeing</string>
    <string name="directions">directions</string>
    <string name="information">information</string>
    <string name="monterey">monterey</string>
    <string name="mumbai">Mumbai</string>
    <string name="first_fragment">first_fragment</string>
    <string name="fourth_fragment">fourth_fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment">second_fragment</string>
    <string name="third_fragment">third_fragment</string>
    <string name="large_text">"-----------SWIPE RIGHT--------\n\n""Mumbai, formerly Bombay, city, capital of Maharashtra state, southwestern India. It is the country’s financial and commercial centre and its principal port on the Arabian Sea..""\n\nLocated on Maharashtra’s coast, Mumbai is India’s most-populous city, and it is one of the largest and most densely populated urban areas in the world. It was  ""built on a site of ancient settlement, and it took its name from the local goddess Mumba—a form of Parvati, the consort of Shiva, one of the principal deities of Hinduism—whose temple once stood in what is now the southeastern section of the city.""Mumbai, long the centre of India’s cotton textile industry, subsequently developed a highly diversified manufacturing sector that included an increasingly important information technology (IT) component. ""\n\nIn addition, the city’s commercial and financial institutions are strong and vigorous, and Mumbai serves as the country’s financial hub. ""\n\nIt suffers, however, from some of the perennial problems of many large expanding industrial cities: air and water pollution, widespread areas of substandard housing, and overcrowding. ""\n\nThe last problem is exacerbated by the physical limits of the city’s island location.""It became known as Bombay during the British colonial period, the name possibly an Anglicized corruption of Mumbai or perhaps of Bom Baim (“Good Harbour”), supposedly a Portuguese name for the locale. ""\nThe name Mumbai was restored officially in 1995, although Bombay remained in common usage.""\n\nCITY SIDE \n\n""The city of Mumbai ""East of the island are the sheltered waters of Mumbai (Bombay) Harbour.""\n\nBombay Island consists of a low-lying plain, about one-fourth of which lies below sea level; the plain is flanked on the east and west by two parallel ridges of low hills.""\n\nThe western ridge terminates at Malabar Hill, which, rising 180 feet (55 metres) above sea level, is one of the highest points in Mumbai. Between Colaba Point and Malabar Hill lies the shallow expanse of Back Bay. On a slightly raised strip of land between the head of Back Bay and the harbour is an area called the Fort, the site of the 17th-century British fortifications (little of which remains standing) within and around which the city grew; From Back Bay the""land stretches northward to the central plain. The extreme northern segment of Mumbai is occupied by a large salt marsh.""\n\nThe old city covered about 26 square miles (67 square km), stretching from Colaba Point on the southern tip of Bombay Island to the areas known as Mahim and Sion on its northern coast.""\n In 1950 Mumbai expanded northward, embracing the large island of Salsette, which was joined to Bombay Island by a causeway. ""\n\nBy 1957 a number of suburban municipal boroughs and some neighbouring villages on Salsette were incorporated into Greater Mumbai—the metropolitan region surrounding Bombay Island and the city itself. "\n\nSince then Greater Mumbai has continued to expand. ""\n\nThe natural beauty of Mumbai is unsurpassed by that of most other cities in the region. "\nThe wide harbour, studded with islands and dotted with the white sails of innumerable small craft, affords secure shelter to ships, particularly when storms lash the coast. ""\n\nThe largest of the harbour’s islands is Elephanta, which is famous for its 8th- and 9th-century Hindu cave temples. ""\n Salsette Island was once the haunt of wild animals such as tigers, leopards, jackals, and deer, but those are no longer found there. Animal life now consists of cows, oxen, sheep, goats, and other domestic species, as well as monkeys.""\n\n Birdlife includes vultures, pigeons, peacocks, cranes, and ducks.""\n\nCLIMATE\n\n""The climate of Mumbai is warm and humid. There are four seasons. Cool weather prevails from December to February and hot weather from March to ""May. The rainy season, brought by monsoon winds from the southwest, lasts from June to September and is followed by the post-monsoon season, lasting through October and November, when the weather is again hot. Mean monthly temperatures vary from 91 °F (33 °C) in May to 67 °F (19 °C) in January. ""Annual rainfall is about 70 inches (1,800 mm), with an average of 24 inches (600 mm) occurring in July alone.\n\n""CITY LAYOUT\n\n ""The older part of Mumbai is much built-up and devoid of vegetation, but the more affluent areas, such as Malabar Hill, contain some greenery; ""there are a number of open playgrounds and parks.""\n\n Most of the older factories are located in that part of the city. ""\n\nMumbai is extremely crowded, and housing is scarce for anyone who is not wealthy. (For that reason, commercial and industrial enterprises have found it increasingly difficult to attract mid-level professional, technical, or managerial staff.) ""\n\nIn an attempt to stem the ongoing immigration of unskilled labour that has increased the city’s indigent and homeless population, city planners have encouraged enterprises to locate across Mumbai Harbour—notably in Navi (“New”) Mumbai—and have banned the development and expansion of industrial units inside the city; their efforts, however, have been largely unsuccessful.""\nMumbai’s architecture is a mixture of florid Gothic Revival styles—characteristic of the United States and Britain in the 18th and 19th centuries—and contemporary designs."\n\n The older administrative and commercial buildings are intermingled with skyscrapers and multistoried concrete-block buildings.""\n\nPEOPLE\n\n""Light and shadow.\n""Mumbai’s growth since the 1940s has been steady if not phenomenal. At the turn of the 20th century its population was some 850,000, by 1950 it had more than doubled, and over the next 50 years it increased nearly 10-fold to exceed 16 million. Population growth continued into the 21st century. The city’s birth rate is much lower than that of the country as a whole because of family-planning programs. ""\nThe high overall growth rate is largely attributable to the influx of people in search of employment. Because of the limited physical expanse of the city, the growth in Mumbai’s population has been accompanied by an astounding increase in population density. By the early 21st century the city had reached an average of some 77,000 persons per square mile (29,500 per square km). Settlement is especially dense in much of the city’s older section; the wealthy areas near Back Bay are less heavily populated.""\n\nECONOMY ""\n\nMumbai is the economic hub and commercial and financial centre of India. Its economic composition in some respects mirrors India’s unique mosaic of prosperity and technological achievement vis-à-vis impoverishment and underdevelopment. While Mumbai contains the Indian Atomic Energy Commission’s establishment, with its nuclear reactors and plutonium separators, many areas on the outskirts of the city continue to rely on traditional biogenic sources of fuel and energy (such as cow dung). ""\n\nMANUFACTURING AND TECHNOLOGY ""\n\nAlthough cotton textile manufacturing, through which Mumbai prospered in the 19th century, remains important to the city’s economy, it has lost much ground to newer industries, especially since the late 20th century. Production of metals, chemicals, automobiles, and electronics along with a host of ancillary industries are now among the city’s major enterprises. Other manufacturing""activities, such as food processing, papermaking, printing, and publishing, also are significant sources of income and employment.""\n\nFINANCE AND OTHER SERVICES""\n\nThe Reserve Bank of India, the country’s central bank, is located in Mumbai. A number of other commercial banks, a government-owned life insurance corporation, and various long-term investment financial institutions also are based in the city. All of those institutions have attracted major financial and business services to Mumbai.""The Bombay Stock Exchange is the country’s leading stock and share market. Although a number of economic hubs sprang up around the country since independence and reduced the exchange’s pre-independence stature, it remains the preeminent centre in volume of financial and other business transacted and serves as a barometer of the country’s economy.\n\n""TRANSPORTATION\n\n""Mumbai is connected by a network of roads to the rest of India. It is the railhead for the Western and Central railways, and trains from the city carry goods and passengers to all parts of the country. ""\nDuring the early 1970s, in an effort to relieve road congestion, Salsette Island was linked to the mainland by a bridge across Thana Creek, the headwaters of Mumbai Harbour. More express highways and more bridges have been built since then. Notable additions to the road network are the Banda-Worli Sea Link (opened 2009), which bridges Mahim Bay on the west side of the city, and a new expressway between eastern Mumbai and Navi Mumbai (opened 2014) that supersedes the earlier Thana Creek bridge.""\n\nCULTURAL LIFE ""\n\nMumbai’s cultural life reflects its ethnically diverse population. The city has a number of museums, libraries, literary organizations, art galleries, theatres, and other cultural institutions. The Chhatrapati Shivaji Maharaj Vastu Sangrahalaya (formerly the Prince of Wales Museum of Western India), housed in a building that is a British architectural mixture of Hindu and Muslim styles, contains three main sections: art, archaeology, and natural history. Nearby is the Jehangir Art Gallery, Mumbai’s first permanent art gallery and a centre for cultural and educational activities. Western and Indian music concerts, festivals, and dance productions are held throughout the year in the city’s many cultural and entertainment facilities. Mumbai also is the centre of the enormous Indian film industry, known as Bollywood, the name derived from an amalgamation of Bombay (the city’s former name) and Hollywood.\n\n""Thanks!\n\n"
        </string>

    <string name="india">India</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_drawer">main_drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="home_second">Home Second</string>
    <string name="animation1">Animation1</string>


</resources>
